[{"Qno":1,"Question":"TCAOAESSI AISCSISTTT","Answer":"ASSOCIATE STATISTICS"},
{"Qno":2,"Question":"CEEUTEX DEAITIEMM ","Answer":"EXECUTE IMMEDIATE"},
{"Qno":3,"Question":"TECRAE IMNOEDINS","Answer":"CREATE DIMENSION"},
{"Qno":4,"Question":"AEIDTLAV CUUTRRTSE","Answer":"VALIDATE STRUCTURE"},
{"Qno":5,"Question":"CTRUNTAE LSRCETU","Answer":"TRUNCATE CLUSTER"},
{"Qno":6,"Question":"RUGPE YENIRCLECB","Answer":"PURGE RECYCLEBIN"},
{"Qno":7,"Question":"PDRO YEDTCORRI","Answer":"DROP DIRECTORY"},
{"Qno":8,"Question":"EST INACSANORTT ","Answer":"SET TRANSACTION"},
{"Qno":9,"Question":"LNAPEIX  LAPNÂ ","Answer":"EXPLAIN PLAN"},
{"Qno":10,"Question":"LRTAE IUOTENL","Answer":"ALTER OUTLINE"},
{"Qno":11,"Question":"ODRP ABLIRRY","Answer":"DROP LIBRARY"},
{"Qno":12,"Question":"AETRL TCERUSL","Answer":"ALTER CLUSTER"}
]
